Guide to the Human Rights Watch records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series 2: Country Files, 1978-1997
  - Human Rights Tribune, 1990-1991 (Box 400, Folder 5)
  - Issues, 1994 (Box 400, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 400, Folder 7)
  - Violations, 1989 June-1992 November (Box 400, Folder 8)
  - Hunan Province--List of Prisons, Labor Camps, 1991-1993 (Box 400, Folder 9)
  - Independent Federation of Chinese Students and Scholars, 1989-1991 (Box 400, Folder 10)
  - Inner Mongolia
  - General, 1984 1991-1996 (Box 400, Folder 11)
  - Report--Robin Munro, 1992 (Box 400, Folder 12)
  - Intellectuals, 1989 March-1990 December (Box 400, Folder 13)
  - International League for Human Rights, 1989-1991 (Box 400, Folder 14)
  - Japan--Treatment of Dissidents--Chinese, 1990-1996, (3 folders) (Box 400, Folder 15-17)
  - Jones, Sidney
  - Notes for talks, 1993 (Box 400, Folder 18)
  - Visa Application, 1993 (Box 400, Folder 19)
  - Journalists, 1989 December -1992 June (Box 400, Folder 20)
  - Keeping Lid On--G7 Meeting, 1995 (Box 400, Folder 21)
  - Kennedy Center for Human Rights, 1994 (Box 400, Folder 22)
  - Kong, Jiesheng--Chinese, 1989 (Box 400, Folder 23)
  - Krupp, Carolyn--U.S. Department of Justice--Torture, 1996 (Box 400, Folder 24)
  - Labor
  - General, 1992-1995, (3 folders) (Box 400, Folder 25-27)
  - Boycotts, 1989-1992 (Box 401, Folder 1)
  - Camps
  - Background, 1991-1994 (Box 401, Folder 2)
  - Testimony, 1991 (Box 401, Folder 3)
  - Forced
  - General, 1991-1995 (Box 401, Folder 4)
  - Exports to Western Countries and Japan, 1991-1995 (Box 401, Folder 5)
  - Information Request, 1991 (Box 401, Folder 6)
  - International Labor, 1989-1994 (Box 401, Folder 7)
  - Prison Labor, 1991 1995 (Box 401, Folder 8)
  - Unions--AFL-CIO and Toycott, 1989-1991 (Box 401, Folder 9)
  - Workers
  - General, 1990 (Box 401, Folder 10)
  - Worker Rights, 1994 (Box 401, Folder 11)
  - Workers Federation, 1989-1990 (Box 401, Folder 12)
  - Working Conditions, undated (Box 401, Folder 13)
  - Laogai Research Foundation
  - Cruel Money: Who Profits from China's Laogai ExportsÀ, 1993 May (Box 401, Folder 14)
  - Laogai Report, 1992-1995 (Box 401, Folder 15)
  - Law--Legal System--General, 1989-1995 (Box 401, Folder 16)
  - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1989-1991 (Box 401, Folder 17)
  - Le Monde, 1989 (Box 401, Folder 18)
  - Liu Gang and Chen Ziming, 1992 (Box 401, Folder 19)
  - Liu Qiang, 1992-1993 (Box 401, Folder 20)
  - Liu Xiaobo, 1989 (Box 401, Folder 21)
  - Lu Jing-hua, 1990 (Box 401, Folder 22)
  - Lui Kin-hong, a/k/a Jerry Lui--Extradition, 1996-1997 (Box 401, Folder 23)
  - Martin, Helmut--Papers re, China's Democracy Movement, 1990 (Box 401, Folder 24)
  - Medical, 1990 (Box 401, Folder 25)
  - Memos, 1992 (Box 401, Folder 26)
  - Military
  - General, 1991-1993 (Box 401, Folder 27)
  - Government, 1988 December -1989 July (Box 401, Folder 28)
  - Minnesota Lawyers International Human Rights Committee--List of Arrests, 1989 (Box 401, Folder 29)
  - Minzhu Zhongguo, 1990 (Box 401, Folder 30)
  - Monitors, 1989-1990 (Box 401, Folder 31)
  - Nanjing Protests, 1995 (Box 401, Folder 32)
  - National Committee on United States-China Relations, 1992 (Box 401, Folder 33)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1989-1991 (Box 401, Folder 34)
  - News Clips, 1993 April -1994 May (5 folders) (Box 401, Folder 35-39)
  - News on Groups and Activities, 1990-1991 (Box 401, Folder 40)
  - Newspaper Front Pages on the Democratic Movement of China '89 (Chinese/English), 1989 (Box 402, Folder 1)
  - Ng, Stephen K.C.--Human Rights for China, 1989 (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - North American Coalition for Chinese Democracy (NACCD), 1990-1991 (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - Northwest Regional China Council--China Information Bulletin, 1990-1992 (Box 402, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear/Atomic Testing--News Clippings, 1993 (Box 402, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Power, 1994 (Box 402, Folder 6)
  - Ohmert, Garry--Imprisonment, 1991-1994 (Box 402, Folder 7)
  - Olympics 2000 Bid
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 402, Folder 8)
  - Press, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 402, Folder 9-10)
  - Organ Transplants and Trafficking, 1992-1995 1997 (Box 402, Folder 11)
  - Orphanages
  - General, 1995-1996 (Box 402, Folder 12)
  - Death by Default, 1995 1997 (Box 402, Folder 13)
  - Shanghai Orphanage Project, 1995 (Box 402, Folder 14)
    [restricted until 2071]
  - Orphans
  - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 402, Folder 15)
    [restricted until 2073]
  - Press, 1994 1996, (5 folders) (Box 402, Folder 16-20)
  - Other Groups--Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 402, Folder 21)
  - Peaceful Evolution, 1992 (Box 402, Folder 22)
    (China Campaign)
  - PEN--Writers in Prison Committee, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 402, Folder 23-24)
  - Persecution After Prison, 1992 (Box 402, Folder 25)
  - Petitions, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 402, Folder 26-27)
  - Phonetic Standard Telegraph Code, 1983 November (Box 402, Folder 28)
  - Politics, 1993-1995 (Box 402, Folder 29)
  - Population--General/Statistics, 1990-1994 (Box 402, Folder 30)
  - Pornography, 1991-1994 (Box 402, Folder 31)
  - Post-June 4th Student--Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 402, Folder 32)
  - Press Chronology, 1990-1993 1996, (6 folders) (Box 403, Folder 1-6)
  - Press Freedom Herald, 1989-1990 (Box 403, Folder 7)
  - Prisoners
  - General, 1989-1990 1993-1995, (5 folders) (Box 403, Folder 8-12)
  - Foundation for Human Rights & Democracy in China--List of Prisoners, 1991 August (Box 403, Folder 13)
  - Schifter, Richard, 1990 (Box 403, Folder 14)
  - U.S. State Department--AW Memo, 1993 (Box 403, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box 403, Folder 16-18)
  - Prisons
  - Conditions, 1989-1995 (Box 403, Folder 19)
    - Lingyuan Prison
      - Groups, 1992 (Box 403, Folder 20)
      - Report, 1991-1992 (Box 403, Folder 21)
      - Research Materials, 1991-1993, (3 folders) (Box 403, Folder 22-24)
      - Research Materials, 1994 (Box 404, Folder 1)
      - Labor
      - General, 1991-1992 (Box 404, Folder 2)
      - Beijing Prison 2--Appendices, 1990 (Box 404, Folder 3)
      - Child Labor, 1991 (Box 404, Folder 4)
      - Price of Obscurity--Press Reports, 1994 (Box 404, Folder 5)
      - Reform Enterprises, 1991-1994 (Box 404, Folder 6)
      - Re-education through Labor, 1994 (Box 404, Folder 7)
      - Workers Autonomous Federation, 1989-1992 (Box 404, Folder 8)
      - Regulations, 1994-1995 (Box 404, Folder 9)
      - Statistics, 1990 1994 (Box 404, Folder 10)
      - Publications--Miscellaneous
      - Chinese, 1990-1993 undated, (5 folders) (Box 404, Folder 11-15)
      - English, 1986 1988-1992 1994-1996 undated, (3 folders) (Box 404, Folder 16-18)
      - Reebok Human Rights Award, 1989-1991 (Box 404, Folder 19)
      - Refugees--Immigration, 1990-1994, (2 folders) (Box 404, Folder 20-21)
      - Religion
      - General, 1989-1992 (Box 404, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence, 1990-1995, (2 folders) (Box 404, Folder 23-24)
        - Analysis, 1993 (Box 404, Folder 25)
        - Asia Watch (AW)
        - Punishment Season--Correspondence, 1990 (Box 404, Folder 26)
        - Work and Contacts, 1991-1994 (Box 404, Folder 27)
        - Carey, Archbishop George, 1994 (Box 404, Folder 28)
        - Congressional Advocacy, 1991-1994 (Box 404, Folder 29)
        - Project on Religion and Human Rights, 1994-1995 (Box 404, Folder 30)
        - Shouters Report, 1994 June (Box 405, Folder 1)
        - Sanctions, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 405, Folder 2-3)
        - Scowcroft Visit, 1989 (Box 405, Folder 4)
        - Secret Societies in the PRC: Their Revival and Suppression in the 1980s, undated (Box 405, Folder 5)
        - Sentencing, 1990-1992 (Box 405, Folder 6)
        - Seymour, Jim
        - Background, 1981 1984-1991 (Box 405, Folder 7)
        - Bingtuan, undated (Box 405, Folder 8)
        - Events, 1990-1993 (Box 405, Folder 9)
        - Shaanxi Province, undated (Box 405, Folder 10)
        - Shanghai Movement, 1989 May -June (Box 405, Folder 11)
        - Sichuan Province, 1994 (Box 405, Folder 12)
        - Smuggling, 1993-1994 (Box 405, Folder 13)
        - Stability, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 405, Folder 14-15)
        - Su Xiaokang (prisoner), 1989 July (Box 405, Folder 16)
        - Suicide, 1993 (Box 405, Folder 17)
        - Taiwan
        - China Relations, 1991-1993 (Box 405, Folder 18)
        - Native People, 1995 (Box 405, Folder 19)
        - Press Clips, 1993-1995 (Box 405, Folder 20-22)
        - Three Gorges Dam Report, 1995-1996 (Box 405, Folder 23)
        - Tiananmen Square Massacre June 3-4, 1989
        - Accounts, 1989 (Box 405, Folder 24)
        - Anniversaries, 1990-1996, (7 folders) (Box 405, Folder 25-31)
        - Articles/Publications, 1989 (Box 405, Folder 32)
        - Articles/Publications, 1989, (3 folders) (Box 406, Folder 1-3)
        - Articles/Publications, 1989, (3 folders) (Box 406, Folder 4-6)
        - Asiaweek, Tiananmen: The Truth, 1989 December (Box 406, Folder 7)
        - "Beijing Spring", undated (Box 406, Folder 8)
        - Echoes From Tiananmen, 1989-1990 (Box 406, Folder 9)
        - Eyewitness Accounts, 1989-1990 (Box 406, Folder 10)
        - "The First Interviews with China's Leaders Since Tiananmen Square", U.S. News & World Report, 1990 March12 (Box 406, Folder 11)
        - Freedom Herald, 1990 July (Box 406, Folder 12)
        - General, 1989-1991, (5 folders) (Box 406, Folder 13-17)
        - Human Rights in China Report, 1993 March (Box 406, Folder 18)
        - International League for Human Rights, "Massacre in Beijing", 1989 (Box 406, Folder 19)
        - June 4th Project--Support Monitoring Group--London
        - Arrests--Lists of, 1989-1991 (Box 406, Folder 20)
        - Correspondence, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 407, Folder 1-2)
        - General, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 407, Folder 3-4)
        - Invitation, 1991-1992 (Box 407, Folder 5)
        - Staff, 1989-1990 (Box 407, Folder 6)
        - Kong, Peter, "Trashing the Hopes of TiananmenÀ", The Nation, 1990 April 23 (Box 407, Folder 7)
        - Tibet
        - Arrests--Lists of, 1991-1992 (Box 407, Folder 8)
        - Australia Tibet Council News, 1994-1995 (Box 407, Folder 9)
        - Australian Campaign for Tibet News, 1992 (Box 407, Folder 10)
        - Birth Control, 1992-1993 (Box 407, Folder 11)
        - Canada Tibet Committee Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 407, Folder 12)
        - Communication w/Government, 1990 (Box 407, Folder 13)
        - Conference, 1993 September (Box 407, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence, 1989-1992 1994-1995 (Box 407, Folder 15)
        - Cutting Off the Serpent's Head: Tightening Control in Tibet, 1994-1995, 1996 March (Box 407, Folder 16)
        - Dalai Lama
        - General, 1989 (Box 407, Folder 17)
        - U.S. Visit, 1995 (Box 407, Folder 18)
        - Demonstrations, 1987-1996, (3 folders) (Box 407, Folder 19-21)
        - Dharamsala--Department of Information and International Relations, 1992-1996 (Box 407, Folder 22)
        - 11th Panchen Lama--Gendhun Choekyi Nyima, 1995 (Box 407, Folder 23)
        - Foreign Relations, 1989-1990 (Box 407, Folder 24)
        - Funding, 1992 (Box 407, Folder 25)
        - General, 1988-1994, (6 folders) (Box 407, Folder 26-31)
        - General, 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 408, Folder 1-3)
        - Tiananmen Square Massacre June 3-4, 1989
        - General, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 408, Folder 4-5)
        - Report, 1989-1990 (Box 408, Folder 6)
        - Special Broadcasting Service (SBS) TV, 1990 (Box 408, Folder 7)
        - Statements, 1989 1993 (Box 408, Folder 8)
        - Testimonial to History, 1989 (Box 408, Folder 9)
        - Tiananmen Archives Post, 1989 June 4, (7 folders) (Box 408, Folder 10-16)
        - Tiananmen Archives Post, undated, (2 folders) (Box 409, Folder 1-2)
        - Statements--U.S. Government--Pro-Democracy Movement, 1989 (Box 409, Folder 3)
        - Tibet
        - Tibet Information Network (TIN), 1990-1996, (3 folders) (Box 409, Folder 4-6)
        - Tibetan Bulletin, 1989-1991 1994 (Box 409, Folder 7)
        - Tibetan Environment & Development News, 1993 1995 (Box 409, Folder 8)
        - Tibetan Review, 1990-1995, (3 folders) (Box 409, Folder 9-11)
        - Tibetan Youth Congress--Rangzen, 1989 (Box 409, Folder 12)
        - Tiger Leopard Youth Association, 1992 (Box 409, Folder 13)
        - Torture
        - General, 1988-1990 (Box 409, Folder 14)
        - Reports--Chinese Press, 1986-1990 (Box 409, Folder 15)
        - United Nations (UN)--Tibet at the 45th Commission on Human Rights, 1989 (Box 409, Folder 16)
        - United States
        - Congressional Advocacy, 1990 (Box 409, Folder 17)
        - Congressional Hearing on Tibet, 1992 (Box 409, Folder 18)
        - House Testimony--Eliot Sperling, 1987 (Box 409, Folder 19)
        - Testimony before Senate Foreign Relations Committee, 1995 (Box 409, Folder 20)
        - U.S. Tibet Committee--Save Tibet Action News, 1991-1992 (Box 409, Folder 21)
        - Women
        - General, 1987-1995, (2 folders) (Box 409, Folder 22-23)
        - Tibetan Women's Association, 1995 (Box 409, Folder 24)
        - Trade (Box 410)
        - General, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 410, Folder 1-2)
        - Aid, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 410, Folder 3-4)
        - Exports to U.S., 1991-1994, (2 folders) (Box 410, Folder 5-6)
        - General, 1993-1995 (Box 410, Folder 7)
        - Human Rights Violations, 1989-1990 (Box 410, Folder 8)
        - International Campaign for Tibet
        - General, 1990 (Box 410, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, 1986-1990 1992-1996 (Box 410, Folder 10)
        - Tibet in China: An International Alert Report, 1988 August (Box 410, Folder 11)
        - Tibet Press Watch, 1988-1995, (3 folders) (Box 410, Folder 12-14)
        - International Committee of Lawyers for Tibet, 1990 1992-1994 (Box 410, Folder 15)
        - International Fund for the Development of Tibet--Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 410, Folder 16)
        - International Human Rights Organizations, 1986-1990 (Box 410, Folder 17)
        - Killings, 1989-1990 (Box 410, Folder 18)
        - Land Issues--Ethnic Groups--Women, 1989-1990 (Box 410, Folder 19)
        - Lungta (wind horse), undated (Box 410, Folder 20)
        - Medical Alerts, 1992-1994 (Box 410, Folder 21)
        - Military and Government, 1989-1990 (Box 410, Folder 22)
        - Missions, 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 410, Folder 23-25)
        - News Tibet, 1988-1995 (Box 411, Folder 1)
        - Political Opposition, 1989-1990 (Box 411, Folder 2)
        - Political Prisoners
        - General, 1992-1994 (Box 411, Folder 3)
        - Detentions and Arrests, 1991-1992 undated, (3 folders) (Box 411, Folder 4-6)
        - Press--General, 1989-1996, (3 folders) (Box 411, Folder 7-9)
        - Press Releases, 1989-1993 (Box 411, Folder 10)
        - Prisons, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 411, Folder 11-12)
        - Refugees, 1989 (Box 411, Folder 13)
        - Snow Lion Newsletter and Catalog, 1994 (Box 411, Folder 14)
        - Tang Daxian Article on Lhasa Massacre, 1989 (Box 411, Folder 15)
        - Translation Project, 1991-1993 (Box 412, Folder 1)
        - Trials
        - General, 1991 (Box 412, Folder 2)
        - Lawyers and Journalists, 1990-1993 (Box 412, Folder 3)
        - Tiananmen and June 4th related Trials, 1989-1991 (Box 412, Folder 4)
        - Union of Catholic Asian News (UCAN), 1990-1994, (15 folders) (Box 412, Folder 5-19)
        - Union of Catholic Asian News (UCAN), 1994-1995, (7 folders) (Box 413, Folder 1-7)
        - Underground Activities in China, 1990 (Box 413, Folder 8)
        - United Nations
        - Commission on Human Rights, 1990-1991 1993, (3 folders) (Box 413, Folder 9-11)
        - Committee Against Torture, 1996 (Box 413, Folder 12)
        - Fourth World Conference on Women, 1995
        - Chinese Delegation Preparations, 1995 (Box 413, Folder 13)
        - Clean-up Site, Visas, Rules, Agreements, 1995 (Box 413, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence/Faxes, 1995 (Box 413, Folder 15)
        - Draft Declaration and the Draft Platform for Action, 1995 May 15 (Box 413, Folder 16)
        - General, 1995, (4 folders) (Box 413, Folder 17-20)
        - Global Faxnet, 1995 (Box 413, Folder 21)
        - Human Rights Watch (HRW)--News Releases, 1995 (Box 413, Folder 22)
        - Media, 1995 (Box 413, Folder 23)
        - Miscellaneous, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 413, Folder 24-25)
        - Press, 1995 (Box 413, Folder 26)
        - Publications (Chinese), 1995 (Box 413, Folder 27)
        - Miscellaneous, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 414, Folder 1-3)
        - News Clips, 1995, (4 folders) (Box 414, Folder 4-7)
        - Non-Governmental Organizations
        - Accreditation, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 8)
        - Activities, pre-activities, official conference, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 9)
        - Officials, agencies, responses, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 10)
        - Press Lists, clips, harassment, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 11)
        - U.N. Documents, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 12)
        - United States--Hillary Clinton, State Dept., Congress and Lobbying, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 13)
        - Wire Services, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 14)
        - Working Group on Human Rights of Women--Minutes, 1995 (Box 414, Folder 15)
        - Fund for Population Activities (UNFPA), 1993 (Box 414, Folder 16)
        - General, 1990-1994 (Box 414, Folder 17-18)
        - General Assembly--Petition Campaign, 1989 September (Box 414, Folder 19)
        - Vienna Conference, 1993 (Box 414, Folder 20)
        - United States
        - Bush Report, 1991-1992 (Box 414, Folder 21)
        - Cabinet--Secretary of Commerce, Ron Brown, 1994 (Box 414, Folder 22)
        - Congress
        - Congressional Advocacy, 1989-1996, (4 folders) (Box 414, Folder 23-26)
        - Hearings--Senate Foreign Relations Committee, 1990 (Box 415, Folder 1)
        - Testimony, 1989-1995 (Box 415, Folder 2)
        - Trip, 1992 (Box 415, Folder 3)
        - U.S. Policy--Congress, 1989-1992 (Box 415, Folder 4)
        - State Department
        - U.S. Reaction to Chinese Events, 1989 (Box 415, Folder 5)
        - Annual Report on Human Rights, 1989 (Box 415, Folder 6)
        - Baker Visit, 1991 (Box 415, Folder 7)
        - General, 1991-1992 (Box 415, Folder 8)
        - Reports--China, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 415, Folder 9-10)
        - U.S.-China
        - Government Documents, 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box 415, Folder 11-13)
        - Official Visits, 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box 415, Folder 14-16)
        - Relations, 1991-1993, (2 folders) (Box 415, Folder 17-18)
        - U.S. Policy
        - Arms, 1991-1994, (2 folders) (Box 415, Folder 19-20)
        - Bilateral Policy--HR Commission, 1992 (Box 415, Folder 21)
        - Carter-Menil Human Rights Prize, 1991 (Box 415, Folder 22)
        - General, 1989-1993, (11 folders) (Box 415, Folder 23-33)
        - General, 1993-1995, (4 folders) (Box 416, Folder 1-4)
        - National Committee on United States-China Relations, 1992 (Box 416, Folder 5)
        - Trade--Most Favored Nation (MFN)
        - General, 1990-1993, (9 folders) (Box 416, Folder 6-14)
        - Pease Bill-H.R. 4939 1990 (Box 416, Folder 15)
        - Sanctions, 1990 (Box 416, Folder 16)
        - Non-MFN, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 416, Folder 17-18)
        - Visa Denials--Bush Executive Order, 1989-1992 (Box 416, Folder 19)
        - U.S.-China Business Council, 1992 (Box 416, Folder 20)
        - Van Ness, Peter, "Analyzing the Impact of International Sanctions on China", 1989 December (Box 416, Folder 21)
        - Vause, W. Gary, "Tibet to Tienanmen: Chinese Human Rights and United States Foreign Policy", Vanderbilt Law Review, 42 (1989), 1989 (Box 416, Folder 22)
        - Vice, 1994-1995 (Box 416, Folder 23)
        - Wang Juntao (Box 417)
        - "The Case of Wang Juntao", UCLA Pacific Basin Law Journal, 10:1 (fall, 1991), 1991 (Box 417, Folder 1)
        - Reports, 1991 (Box 417, Folder 2)
        - Washington Center for China Studies--China Report, 1990 (Box 417, Folder 3)
        - White Paper on Criminal Reform, 1992 (Box 417, Folder 4)
        - Wires, 1990-1992, (15 folders) (Box 417, Folder 5-19)
        - Wires, 1993, (3 folders) (Box 418, Folder 1-3)
        - Witness Reports on the Democratic Movement of China '89, 1990 May (Box 418, Folder 4)
        - Woo, Roger, "The Project for Tiananmen Square", 1990 (Box 418, Folder 5)
        - World Bank, 1989-1995 (Box 418, Folder 6)
        - Wu, Harry (activist), 1990-1993 (Box 418, Folder 7)
        - Xinhua News Agency, 1990-1991 (Box 418, Folder 8)
        - Xinjiang--Ethnic Separatism and Government Reaction, 1990-1995, (6 folders) (Box 418, Folder 9-14)
        - Xu Gang--Environmental Damage--Chinese, 1988 (Box 418, Folder 15)
        - Youth, 1991-1994 (Box 418, Folder 16)
        - Zhang Sizhi--Resume, 1992 (Box 418, Folder 17)
        - Zhao Ziyang, 1990-1992 (Box 418, Folder 18)
        - Zhong Shi-Lin--Chinese Student Lawsuit, 1990 (Box 418, Folder 19)
        - Hong Kong
        - Asia Watch
        - Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 418, Folder 20)
        - Work, 1988-1991 (Box 418, Folder 21)
        - "April Fifth Action" Case, 1989-1990 (Box 418, Folder 22)
        - Asia Monitor Resource Center, 1990 (Box 418, Folder 23)
        - Bill of Rights Bulletin, 1992-1994 (Box 418, Folder 24)
        - Boat People--Clippings, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 418, Folder 25-26)
        - Britain, 1989-1991 (Box 418, Folder 27)
        - China Relations re, 1997 1989-1991 (Box 418, Folder 28)
        - Communications w/Government, 1989-1990 (Box 418, Folder 29)
        - Correspondence--General, 1990-1991 (Box 418, Folder 30)
        - Demonstrations, 1989 (Box 418, Folder 31)
        - Foreign Relations, 1989-1991 (Box 418, Folder 32)
        - General, 1988-1993, (5 folders) (Box 418, Folder 33-37)
        - Groups/Contacts, undated (Box 418, Folder 38)
        - Hong Kong Digest, 1992-1996 (Box 418, Folder 39)
        - Human Rights Groups, 1990-1991 (Box 418, Folder 40)
        - Human Rights Violations, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 418, Folder 41-42)
        - International Human Rights Organizations, 1989-1991 (Box 418, Folder 43)
        - Kin Chi Faxes, 1989 (Box 418, Folder 44)
        - Legal System/Texts, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 419, Folder 1-2)
        - Military and Government, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 419, Folder 3-5)
        - Missions/Visits, 1989-1990 (Box 419, Folder 6)
        - News Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 419, Folder 7)
        - Political Opposition, 1989-1990 (Box 419, Folder 8)
        - Press, 1989-1991 (Box 419, Folder 9)
        - Refugees
        - General, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 419, Folder 10-11)
        - Vietnamese
        - Interviews, undated, (3 folders) (Box 419, Folder 12-14)
        - Mission Research, 1990 (Box 419, Folder 15)
        - Strossen, Nadine--Hong Kong Visit, 1988 January (Box 419, Folder 16)
        - Theologides, Stergios "Terry"--Resume, 1989 (Box 419, Folder 17)
        - The Tiananmen University of Democracy (Chinese), 1990 (Box 419, Folder 18)
        - Trade and Aid, 1989-1991 (Box 419, Folder 19)
        - Trade Unions Labor Rights, 1990-1991 (Box 419, Folder 20)
        - Trini Leung--Workers' Autonomous Federation Overseas of China (WAFOU), 1990 May (Box 419, Folder 21)
        - India
        - Asia Watch (AW)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 419, Folder 22)
        - Andhra Pradesh, 1991-1992 (Box 419, Folder 23)
        - Work, 1988-1995, (3 folders) (Box 419, Folder 24-26)
        - "Assam Massacre" Report
        - Ahmed, Rafiq, "The Assam Massacre", 1983 (Box 419, Folder 27)
        - General, 1991-1993, (3 folders) (Box 419, Folder 28-30)
        - Clippings, 1990-1993, (2 folders) (Box 419, Folder 31-32)
        - Ayodhya--Hindu-Muslim Violence, 1991-1992 (Box 420, Folder 1)